<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en-US" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://egrimesdirect.com/blogs/news.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://egrimesdirect.com/blogs/news"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://egrimesdirect.com/blogs/news.atom"/>
  <title>eGrimesDirect - More Information</title>
  <updated>2021-07-08T13:40:32-04:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>eGrimesDirect</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://egrimesdirect.com/blogs/news/news-release-3m-1870-aura-health-care-respirator-and-surgical-masks</id>
    <published>2021-07-08T13:40:32-04:00</published>
    <updated>2021-07-08T13:46:33-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://egrimesdirect.com/blogs/news/news-release-3m-1870-aura-health-care-respirator-and-surgical-masks"/>
    <title>News Release 3M 1870+ Aura Health Care Respirator and Surgical Masks</title>
    <author>
      <name>Shopify API</name>
    </author>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://egrimesdirect.com/blogs/news/egrimesdirect-for-consumers</id>
    <published>2018-02-26T21:19:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2020-01-22T16:07:19-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://egrimesdirect.com/blogs/news/egrimesdirect-for-consumers"/>
    <title>eGrimesDirect for Consumers</title>
    <author>
      <name>Lorii Myers</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[We are a wholesale company just as Costco is. Although the quantities we sell may be greater than what you would normally buy, the savings should be well worth it.<p><a class="read-more" href="https://egrimesdirect.com/blogs/news/egrimesdirect-for-consumers">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[Consumers<br><br>Some interesting eGrimesDirect facts for consumers:<br><br>We are a wholesale company just as Costco is. Although the quantities we sell may be greater than what you would normally buy, the savings should be well worth it.<br><br>Many of our preferred suppliers produce both industrial and consumer products. We are thrilled to have the opportunity to bring these new and established brands to market.<br><br>We also offer our own private brands TUFF GRADE &amp; EGD which include a full line of rugged, quality products suitable for consumer and industry use.<br><br>. . . and we are adding new products weekly so be sure to check back because as a member you are privy to flash buys, specials and bulk pricing.]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://egrimesdirect.com/blogs/news/egrimesdirect-for-purchasers</id>
    <published>2018-02-26T21:17:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2019-11-26T09:25:07-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://egrimesdirect.com/blogs/news/egrimesdirect-for-purchasers"/>
    <title>eGrimesDirect for Purchasers</title>
    <author>
      <name>Lorii Myers</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[The Grimes NeXus Supply Management Portal helps purchasers to increase efficiency and improve productivity for an enhanced competitive advantage.<p><a class="read-more" href="https://egrimesdirect.com/blogs/news/egrimesdirect-for-purchasers">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[Purchasers<br><br>The Grimes NeXus Supply Management Portal helps purchasers to increase efficiency and improve productivity for an enhanced competitive advantage.<br><br>Whether for single-facility or multiple-plant operation, NeXus will help leverage buying power, standardize and consolidate product sourcing and reduce transactional costs.<br><br>Our product managers take great pride in sourcing the finest products available in the market today. We endeavor to carry a mix of quality and price points that will bring value to your business.<br><br>Buy Smart:<br><br>The NeXus Supply Management Portal makes purchasing efficient and easy by offering the following:<br><br>Advanced Searchability * Quick Ordering Options * Order Approval Workflows * Detailed Account Control * Ability to Track Order Status * Access to History * Enhanced Reporting * Contract Pricing * Rebate Program * Ongoing Addition of User Options and Enhancements <br><br>Buy Quality: <br><br>We showcase the best and brightest products in the marketplace today. Our robust supplier relationships offer Grimes customers' unparalleled first-choice access to new products and technical innovations, and the reassurance of superior product quality and value associated with the brands we have chosen to represent.<br><br>Buy Direct: <br><br>We leverage our buying power to deliver consistent everyday low pricing and the following:<br><br>Massive Product Selection<br>Volume and Large Buy Pricing<br>New Product Lines Added Weekly<br>First Hand Notification of New Product and Technology Solutions by Industry.]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://egrimesdirect.com/blogs/news/egrimesdirect-for-business-owners</id>
    <published>2018-02-26T21:16:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2019-11-26T09:25:07-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://egrimesdirect.com/blogs/news/egrimesdirect-for-business-owners"/>
    <title>eGrimesDirect for Business Owners</title>
    <author>
      <name>Lorii Myers</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[Competitive pricing, fast first-choice access to the right product for the job, assurance of superior quality and reliable, well-informed service are the cornerstones of Grimes' success.<p><a class="read-more" href="https://egrimesdirect.com/blogs/news/egrimesdirect-for-business-owners">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[Business Owners<br><br>Competitive pricing, fast first-choice access to the right product for the job, assurance of superior quality and reliable, well-informed service are the cornerstones of Grimes' success. On the supply side of the business equation, Grimes product managers maintain close watch for innovative products and new technologies. On the demand side, we listen to our customers and anticipate their wants. We value long-term productive customer relationships, and we work hard to earn our customers' confidence and keep their trust.<br><br>Grimes is successful because we put our customers' needs first, and because we understand the what's and whys of what they do in the context of an increasingly competitive business environment. We've found that many Grimes customers, large and small, have identified the need to improve their industrial products purchasing and supply management processes to achieve greater efficiency and enhanced productivity.<br><br>For this reason, we developed the Grimes NeXus Supply Management Portal which is geared to reduce overall procurement costs in acquiring and inventorying all kinds of industrial supplies, materials and tools. Our goals are to ensure that you obtain the best pricing and receive the best value possible in buying the right products for the job, and that those products will be at hand when needed.<br><br>Grimes product management team endeavors to source the "best and brightest" product solutions, promotions, and optimal buying opportunities. Our experience, in-depth product knowledge and applications expertise have led us to develop particularly effective supply management strategies and it is our goal to strengthen your operations and administration through:<br><br>Better pricing and quality-for-money value,<br>Reliable timely supply of all kinds of industrial product needs,<br>Specific identification of what's required for what job,<br>Customized billing and standardized procedures for administrative consistency,<br>Reduced paperwork volumes,<br>Enhanced procurement cost oversight and tracking,<br>Increased control of tools, materials and supplies inventory, and the convenience of a single-source supplier.]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
</feed>
